(Amy:)We're never getting our drinks.
(Bernadette:)No, but we knew that.
(Penny:)Hey, can I start you off
with something to drink?
(Lucy:)-Oh, water would be great.
-Okay.
(Penny:)You're Lucy, right?
I'm a friend of Raj Koothrappali's.
(Penny:)Actually Amy recognized you.
(Lucy:)Wow. How's he doing?
(Penny:)Oh, you know, he's good.
(Lucy:)Great.
(Penny:)Yeah, this is none of my business.
(Penny:)But why did you break up
with him in an e-mail?
(Lucy:)Oh, I don't know.
(Lucy:)I guess I thought it would be easier.
(Penny:)Yeah, I get that.
I'll go get you your water.
When you say "easier,"
(Penny:)you mean easier for you, right?
'Cause it certainly
didn't make it easier for him.
(Lucy:)Any chance I can get
a different waitress?
(Penny:)I'm sorry, this is rude of me.
I will get that water.